federaljobsearch.com 2010-11-20

# Federal Job Search Privacy Policy and Terms

This privacy policy applies to the websites of americajob.com and GovernmentJobSearch.com.  Effective date: May 1, 2006.

Federal Job Search is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the site [http://www.americajob.com](http://www.americajob.com/) and [http://www.governmentjobsearch.com](http://www.governmentjobsearch.com/) .  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Julie Chipman at custservice@americajob.com.  If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php.  TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

## Registration

In order to receive job search alert emails and to fully use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form by submitting your email address, name and a password. **We do not share your email address with any third parties** or advertisers.   We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest, specifically to send you matches to your job search profile.  You have the option to provide additional information (such as  desired income level, job location and job titles) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. 

MissionSoft Incorporated  is the sole owner of the information collected on Federal Job Search or Government Job Search. MissionSoft Incorporated collects limited personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

## Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and billing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).  We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.  Upon completion of any purchase the customer will receive a confirmation email from our transaction provider as a record of the transaction.

## Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We may choose to share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers.  This information does not identify individual users. We currently do not share any such information.

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.  __

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

## Agents 

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

**Service Providers**

We use iTransact Corporation to provide online transaction processing on our site.  When you sign up for premium subscription service or purchase our online guidebook, we will share your name, address and billing information as necessary for the third party to complete the online transaction. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to  your job search account (which contains the personally identifiable information of name, email and search information that you submit while on our site).

We use persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.  We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

**Information Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  To learn more about SSL, follow this link http://www.verisign.com.  

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Your profile is protected by user id and password access only. We do not store any financial information such as credit card information or checking account data. All payments and orders are processed by a highly-respected, secure transaction processor, Itransact Corporation. 

**Additional Terms - Copyright**

The information within this website is copyrighted,no person may resell or repackage this information in any way shape or form. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at custservice@americajob.com.

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

## Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.  For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our job search emails, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each job search alert email or by emailing us at jobs@americajob.com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our customer search menu, or you may contact us at jobs@americajob.com or by mail to Federal Job Search at 609 East Market Street, Suite 103, Charlottesville, VA 22902.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. You may remove information from our database in order not to receive future communications or to cease using our service by doing one of the following: 

1.            Select "Contact Us" from anywhere in the web site, or choose "Send us your feedback" from your customer menu. Then choose comment type "Please cancel my account." This will terminate your service. 

2.             You can send us an email message requesting cancellation of your service to [jobs@americajob.com](mailto:jobs@americajob.com?subject=remove\(cid=79132\)). Please remember to include your customer id, which is included in every email, and your email address.

3.         Log into your account and choose “Terminate Account” from your customer menu.

You have the following options for changing information previously provided:

1.               Visit [http://www.americajob.com](http://www.americajob.com/default.asp?cid=79132&tid=77316), log onto your account by entering your email address and password and then modify your profile . 

2.               When you receive an email job report, use the link provided to allow you to modify or deactivate your profile.

**Change of Policy Notice**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our practices or your dealings with us, you can contact: [jobs@americajob.com](mailto:jobs@americajob.com).
